Okay, sorry. Hey, what's up, Dave?
How are you?
What was going on? I would say I kind of like on me out a little bit and
I wanted to kind of over the bright black screen. Yeah, I uh, I think I ended it. Hey, what's up Mikey?
Hey guys
I think you're being here
Yeah, I appreciate you guys
So
What's up today guys Monday 723 June 23rd
anything interesting going on?
Monday, fun day.
I like you a lot, I think you get me like...
I think you get the show.
You're studying good.
Sitting anything interesting are you you in the?
No, you're okay. Yeah, I'll get around city. Yeah
Well, I do I do love study
No, actually, you know, I kind of like sometimes on my show I like to teach sometimes or like I like to reset
But by doing that I learn it cuz it's like I'm I'm being sent with material again. Oh theology. Oh awesome
My intentions are good even though I might be a little crazy. It's okay. I don't feel crazy, too
Hey sassy
Love you sassy. Thank you
Yeah, thank you guys for being here seems like I don't know seems like maybe
I don't know what it is. I think it feels like, like, there's a lot of people either
turned against me or never really there or
I think it's really hard to trust people, you know
You know if you should be you know your climate yeah
I got a recall of the cuckoo for cocoa puffs climate
People attack turn against you cuz you are kind they see you target. It's a you know, it works. Yeah
It's like no, it's just like that
Just seems like some of the trolling is like just
And let's just figure it does weird since there's we just weird stuff going on hard to describe
But if anybody
Anybody can give it a try if you'll get a start if they notice anything weird, I mean, we know there's been weird stuff going on
But it's because it was like there's so many one day and like so many friends
Hi, maya, how are you thank you for coming
Yeah, I mean chess usually in chess good
And especially since like hey, what's up Sam and think the chance good. I think the chats also
But that's the thing it's like
Like a lot of people like love people aren't coming you chat anymore
So if you mean people are here, I mean, so whether you know whether they like me or hate me, that's fine
Or whatever they say
And then it's like the only person that was coming to the panel was Mr. Bigpipes.
And then, I mean, I was on there with Summer and, you know, EZ from Friendsworth.
And I, like, I love EZ.
I love Summer.
And then all, just Mr. Bigpipes started, like, being really, like,
I get all your messages. Oh, well, you have
Minus 15 likes or we're ever putting minus 15 15 likes whatever Mr. Big Pipe's come along
so I had like three n- I had like three likes or something and
Yeah
And then I asked Mr. Big Pipe was like just like laughing about it
I was like, well, isn't that kind of weird like I have somebody like following me following you to my chat
Post like taking away of stuff and you and you seem like you know him or something
Yeah, let's obviously I mean what do you make it basis?
discord
But this court that all
What's wrong
Big pipes to see fool said 15 of the world is not ready for gay tarot card
We're especially expecting someone with big boobs
Oh, yeah, but it's like, you know
There are there they're there are male terror carburetors with 60,000 to 100 subscribers, you know, they're very
You know, it's like
There's very successful like males
pipes is bad news. No, it's okay. That's okay
I I wanted to ban pipes because pipe came on the other day like, you know
calling me or just doing the n-word bomb right and then I was like you're banned
and then he came back and then I was like you know I had a people I was like
hey well mr. Big Pisces is in the back what do you think so should I have him on
or not I'll leave it to the panel because I was kind of feeling kind of
forgiving I had a kind of fun night last night
And they're like, oh yeah, you can bring him on and then he, you know, he was, and then he played the same song for like a, it was just a weird song and then, um, I mean, it's just a nice song.
Like, you know, we're having fun joking around like, oh, you know, Mr.
Because it's talking about oh, you know, he said you got pegged and stuff like that
And I was you know, I thought I asked him questions and then I can't then it's kind of like
The story just didn't seem authentic. It kind of seemed like he was truly and I don't just like I don't know
And then and then he was like, oh, you got to hook up with sake you didn't say I'm like, oh, no
and then they're talking about
Dr. Pepper
I was a doctor pepper. I don't have dr. Pepper bottled to his butt or something
Got was relevant to that but somehow that
Like I don't know. I don't want to hear any more of the stories
But then I you know, there was just a one-on-one with him and he was just being so weird
Like oh and also he's like he's been using this like
this avatar. Anyone familiar with Chaos Magic? I don't know if you know about
Discordianism.
You know, if you studied Austin Spare.
Fidgiles, but it looks like what someone was saying that his
his stream mirror photo was the Chaos Magic Fidgile. And then
Also, Ziggy was using a Croatia,
which is a magical sigil.
And it's like, you know, some people,
oh, you know, oh, it's like a cool pattern.
It's a cool design.
Like these are actually magical sigils, right?
And yeah, did you see it?
It's like, you know, it's like a sideways triangle.
Croatia, I mean, so magical, they are powerful.
And if they're especially, they're like left out
and stuff like that.
Or put out like on as a profile picture in this broadcast. It's kind of like that makes it more powerful, right?
You hardly know you hardly know me or
Yeah, cuz I studied a steady
You know mad I said the Alistair Crowley magic chaos magic
There's let me there's chaos magic the billions of resistance to it so there's you can be a lot of different
So I don't know. I thought I thought it was like the logo for his computer company
But then he kept insisting on using it he went and then he would like he continued playing songs over and over and over and that it's like
They kind of like just like Charles Vance me kind of stuff
He needs my glass and yet my glass. I don't have glasses. I wish I had my glasses. I had I have had cows
Hit me with their fists. That's my excuse
No one
Everyone doing nice to see everybody. Thanks for being here you guys hit the like you know
Yeah, that's what but then I was so but it's you know, I have to trust my gut
Officially says I mean it's like I got I really did come I can't believe I'm still at my channel. You know came
Be like I'm just lucky to have I feel like there's a reason I haven't and I'm not gonna
I could have a limited time. Who knows? I don't know, you know, who knows how long monetization would last, who knows how, you know
How long this will continue to be a lot of fun for me. It's a lot of fun now
It's getting it gets a little less fun with like all the emotional like
like people like just like
Tell me to fuck off and stuff
That's not complaining. I
Have always been
pretty much the alpha not well not an alpha male but a stigma alpha alpha but
alpha meaning like you know I've been like one but I mean like more of a
lone wolf do you know any Vagos members out there in LA Vagos, D-A-G-O-S as a
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, big pipes.
I bet you looked at it with your spectacles.
Yeah, I don't have any, I mean, it's like I,
I had lasik eye surgery,
but my eyes have just been like, I don't know,
I don't, I don't, I don't remember my lasik,
that was very, that was very near-sighted and had lasik
and it was corrected and now I know,
that's my lasik, my wearing off a little bit.
So Eric yes, so what when second you went worse about outside cops always
Kind of arrest him cuz they think separate genre escape. Yep
So weird question
Yeah, no, it's like I deal in some weird shit, it's like
You're just becoming old happens to us all I don't know
Kind of I'm pretty
Pretty observant
But yeah, then again, you know
I've been smoking weed and you know weed does make a parent a little bit
Who wants to live forever? Oh, not me. I mean, you know not here
I want to live, I've already passed my life expectancy.
The average gay man lives like 33 years old or something.
At the drug store, you can pick up
some generic near sighted glasses for a couple of bucks.
Yeah, and I'll try to go to,
I'll go maybe go to, I guess you guessed it.
Actually, I don't know, I have a coupon somewhere,
I don't know where, I have to find a $10, I have a $210.
Oh, it's before, yeah, I should have a $10 coupon for CVS.
Hi, babe
The jokes, yeah, thank you. Thank you, Hannah. Thank you for the advice
Get some spectacles
Yeah, and if this business it's pretty weird like a in my last yeah, I think there were like 30 people in there, but it's like
Nobody was talking
Those are just people like watching we need to see what if I like
It's only embarrassing the but because our destroyers outlawed motorcycle club also known as the Green Nations of Davis Motorcycle Club, okay
Do I know any Bob West members? No, I would I really
Do not know any motorcycle gang members
The only one I knew I knew this lady X X, but she I don't she likes me anymore, but I don't think she was active in a gang, but
Yeah, I kind of like you know
Try it. I don't talk to anybody here really. I don't talk to I talk to people on the on YouTube
I don't know many people
Yeah, I mean by some because these tarot cards by my villains cards
It's really small and I'm like finding myself. I can't think I can't believe I'm like reading so slow
So
Okay, so I got
You know we I was at a party in a
Hub became an angel support club
Hey, Dougie Dougie, what's up, dude?
Yeah, Dougie, I think I took some of your advice and I I unmodded everybody so there's nobody's a month
nobody's a month
And that's not because anybody did anything wrong or like the mods were not good months
But my mods were just being so harassed and it's like I don't want
Anyone to be harassed for being associated with me, you know
But I have
I'm like I'm really
I didn't like people like constantly asking for rent shoes and then like complain about people
Oh, they have a wrench they have a rent. I don't have a wrench. Please wrench me. I need help
And it was hey, how many?
Yeah
That's pretty crazy is she blond who blond
Right
Or is someone else
So, what do you, what do you, what do you,
what do you, what do you, what do you,
Who blonde though are you saying spanky?
Did I sleep again
No, no one's answer. I mean, yes, it's usually I don't know you're seeing watching me
Yeah
So peeing in a peeing on screen
I didn't hear a question I don't I don't I don't know it's like why aren't people being so weird
Maybe I'm weird. I did a I did smoke a DMT last night and so
Maybe a couple times it was again bomb
That's okay
It's no no lover answer anyway
If I could get, if I would have people, you know,
cards say I'm gonna get lucky.
Oh, so, no, if I had, I mean.
It was like when I was in Glendale.
and it was like, and I had my, I had my house frat, oh, here we go.
What is it, Sike? How you doing? Good morning, how are you?
Pretty good. So, what did you do? You took everybody's rent, right? Now, not a single
mod, right? That's- Yeah, not a single mod.
Yeah, I know people who do that it seems to work work pretty well
It's one way like you said to keep all the fucking infighting out, right? Yeah. Yeah, and also I was just having a
People like yelling at my mods and like oh
Screaming mom and mods and like and asking for modern and it was just like there's it was taking so much energy from the start
It sucks all the life out of the thing. Yeah
Yeah, I
I generally go the other way.
I have everybody modded because I want them all
to self promote and connect with each other.
But then what I do literally is I have everybody modded,
like everybody, which is about the same thing, yeah.
Yeah, and it's just like, but yeah,
I was kind of just worried that, you know,
my models were getting pretty stressed out and, you know,
Um, so I think it's just better if I if I take care of all I've been a mod and a lot of big cats
I can mod myself. It's kind of
It's a little bit more cumbersome, but and I do have kind of a big chat. I'm considering maybe like
Maybe one or two if they were if they really want to be a mod
That I've known for a long long time like you know since the beginning of the show, but
Even though I'm gonna say I'd rather have everybody just get to relax and not have to worry about
Just like saying the right thing is the mod
Yeah
So that worked well for my show, but you know I had go through ups and downs in the show
It seems like you know it seems like a lot of people have turned on me
lately, you know a lot of like close friends
Close friends. Yeah, I beat a beta
Well, you know that you know beat is close, but like not
She's like the closest but then you know my no Joker. I don't know if you know Joker TV
and then
Just and then just other people too like you know that were
I've gone through a bunch of friendships on YouTube and then people just turned on me
I give people a million chances, but people and people like it seems to turn on me and like
But
I'm talking to Hannah and scum a hello scum a
What's his name Ilja is that Ilja Ilja? Yeah
Yeah, and so I mean it's like I understand like you know, uh, you know
I'll have to continue to build my channel.
It's just a small channel, so it's
going to have a completely different audience later.
But it's interesting that the changes
have gone through and what's happened and stuff.
But I'm still having fun.
I'm just trying to tweak it to make it the best experience
for everybody.
Yeah, it's funny.
Over time.
People in the chat they all change. I have all different people now that were there like say a year ago
Not all different, but a lot of different people and
When I first started streaming I had mostly a lot
I had a lot of knuckleheads in my chat as time went by they stopped coming
You know what I mean the knuckleheads. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah
It's like yeah, because I've had like you know, I started I had some chats with like over a hundred people in them
and you know
and then it's like
But I know my numbers are still good. I mean it's everything's going good. It's just like, you know, it's like I guess I miss I miss certain people and
I just stream a lot so I do know I like look back so much shims and some of them. I'm like I look like I
Look pretty bad. I love so I'm trying to be like, you know, I just like I got a lot of my house clean last night. I'm trying to
Maybe I'll get a haircut today or something. I don't know if I'll get a haircut. I think I might look good
Get a haircut. Yeah, I'm gonna get a haircut. Hope you well
Also, I think I'm for 22 bucks down the street like something like Japanese place
Asian place. I haven't had a haircut about a year
Yeah, let's see a night. Oh, there's Timmy, you know tiny Tim tiny times. I said Dougie
Doug take a break from slapping ass and join the panel. Yeah. Thank you
Yeah, well today like, you know, it was just like Mr. Big Pipes came on the panel and he was just like a really bizarre experience
It's just like it seems like he was like
Acting or something. It's just like he was like saying he's acting so weird and like it's a big part of the banjo player
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, he continues to come to my show and like, you know
He'll sit in my show for like hours in the morning a drunk and like just like screaming in the shade of like nonsense and then
Then tonight
Like now he's like getting all sexual with me and it's like yeah
I was like a taste of my own medicine because I would always I think I was you know
I always tell people everything you can probably get on him. He sent me pictures of his
Not as dick-pick, but it's like his outline
Now now it's like now as they turn into like he's like he's like
They'll say oh, I want to
Have oral sex with you with any and then he'll like insult me and then like and then tonight
Like he was like talking about he was trying to tell a story about how he got pegged for two hours
with like a butt plug and a
Dildo by some like muscular woman. I mean it's just like all this
It was these strange stories and it was like funny for a while
And then it's like and then it turned into like oh, and then you put a doctor pepper bottle in his butt
Yeah, I mean and it's just and it's just really like
Yeah. Yeah, we don't we don't have all that kind of crap in my tab and people don't come up and talk like that
Yeah, I went to your live stream last yesterday. I think that's a fake gym. Nick. That's a fake gym. Nick. I don't know
I think I think I know I think
Hey, Spanky hot chocolate weather
I think it's a fake gimmick
because she's got nothing
posted on a channel at all.
And I'm not subbed to them.
And I am subbed to gimmick.
Yep.
So there you go.
That's a fake gimmick.
I believe.
So I think fake gimmicks just cause
a bunch of trouble.
I mean, I'm going to have to like
I'm trying to be, I'm trying to be more like better because I literally had to like end
my stream probably 10 times like the other night because I was just continually getting
poor moms and and we're bombed and then not only like just the bombs, it was just a guest
on the show where they continually do things that I can see less and then they would argue
with me about them.
So I'm getting a lot better.
And I'm working on getting better with boundaries and like just saying saying no
I mean in the no means no kind of thing. It's a good. It's I get fuck
I don't I don't argue about I would listen in the other day when that guy was up here pleading with you to give him a wrench
And you told him no every way
Every way you could you know no no no no he kept asking right that's fucking annoying. I wouldn't got rid of that guy, but
Yeah, yeah, and it's like yeah, and that's like
This is takes I mean, it's like I don't I don't I can't sit here for hours
Talking about like that and it's not even you know
It should be like people that want to support the show or that and that was that I know and trust
Not like there's a lot of people that just wanted for their own agenda
Then and some people were doing rogue mod stuff like hiding like a hundred people in chat
And putting words in the words like my own name like my name on the band words list
And so you know if you ask me a question and stuff like that
To be able to put names on your band wordless managing mom met managing mother that's
They want to be careful who you make a managing lot
See that's the thing of my place everybody is a standard mod except they have about four managing mods
Right everyone else is a standard one so they can't start
What they can't do is come in later. They can go on your channel to yesterday's live stream go in there and start banning people
Hmm, you know they mean the mom. Yeah
They can do that
That's how that's how they do it without people noticing because people would notice there are other problems with notice that
They did it while they're there, but you can go back to the old live chat replays and
To the modding from there. So that's pretty crazy
I had someone do that to me once go on my old live replay and ban like a hundred people out of my shit
That was before that was before I gave everybody a wrench when I used to just have
You know a couple wrenches
So then you have to be careful, right because some people, you know, some people will just
You know, they'll seem like they're great people everything but then of course they have an agenda. You don't know about you know
I mean
Their agenda involves people in your chat. You and you don't even know it. You know what I mean? Yeah
Well, that's the problem like they're because with you know, JTA you saw like they're like what some of the stuff that they've been
Kept posting out co-posting his video where he was it was a video of somebody else had posted on YouTube and so the thumbnail is like
That he's got his disabled daughter that this other guy that he took the and he's been fighting with this guy and
He posted that on his and his
Now that he kept posting on my chat and that because he asked me for any he was modded twice
Somehow and he kept posting it right and then so I am and then
He then he was argue about what he once deposed it or he and then he would they would put different people's profile pictures in their stream yard
They go up they go up places with pictures of me and their avatar. Yeah
Yeah, I mean some people don't mind if they're pictures out but it's like I mean that one of the pictures included like a woman's like a woman's breast cancer car
Scar picture from Facebook and things like that and it's like and just harassing this woman and
Man came on the other night when I was that was his daughter that that was disabled and then he was he and his wife were sitting there almost in tears and stuff
So
I think it's just I think when people go and chat I seen some here this morning and say stupid shit
It doesn't bother me at all. It just makes them look stupid. They're just showing how stupid they are, right?
That's all so I but some people I do understand that some people don't like it and it bothers them
you know and
And and the people do it intentionally because they know that it tweaks them, right? Yeah
Right, I mean it's like that's you know, that's part of the trolling thing is like they're trying to get a reaction and
They're
You're trying to disturb the piece of trying to keep the show off track. They're trying to cause chaos, right? Yeah, but
That's another thing. It's like some of these
Like mr. Bigpipes like some he was using you know, he just keeps coming up with this
His camera works, but he keeps coming up just with this big big big banner
And then someone told me and I know I've studied like a little bit of you know
Chaos magic and I've heard you know discord inism and
Austin Spare, they do these sigils, you know, the sigils, they're sigils and things and people have been using some of these sigils on my, as their things.
And then some of them, one's the demonic sigil from the Goetia, and then this one tonight on big pipes was like a chaos magic sigil, which is like, you know, kind of like putting it out, you know, in their view, it makes it more powerful.
I know a lot of these people for a while. Who do we got here? It's Ilja. How do you pronounce that? Ilja? Oh
Yeah, Ilya oh Ilya mm-hmm. Are you are you're wearing pants today?
We're in a kilt he's got his kilt on
There's where I kill you range the end of the kill
Don't don't don't say this is tell me yes or no
Kilton's foreign because I'm drinking this
Oh, you're the dream of Johnny Johnny's that's label five, okay
It's from school. I've got I've got lifted lifting tea is what I got
I've got a nice harder one. Are you pretty stand are you pretty do you?
Yeah
It's only nine in the morning here, so I'm yeah
I'll go upstairs and have a smoke in a bed. I can't smoke down here in my living room. You know what I mean?
Wow
Can I sing you a song, a score this song for you?
Of course, I want to use, oh, I'm sure it will sound wonderful with your accent.
So what's the tartan? What clan is the tartan on you killed, Ilya?
It's a secret, but now I will sing this song for you and for all the charts, for everyone.
A secret clan, huh? Okay.
I think most cops will go.
They've been gone
In a cold cold crown
Where are four
Many more have gone
When they come
I'll stand my crown
Stand my crown
I'll never be afraid
Yeah, beautiful
Yeah, so, you know, I'm a I have a huge Scottish Irish
genetic ancestry, so I
I
Resonate with some of that
Did you recognize this song, which I was singing?
No, I didn't recognize it, but it's a beautiful song.
I never heard it in a Russian accent.
You have seen the American War movie called...
What was it? From Vietnam War with Mel Gibson.
You know most I don't know
Mel Gibson Mel Gibson has done only one war movie from the other Vietnam war movie
No idea I
Don't watch movies generally. I
Haven't I haven't for a long time anyway. Mm-hmm. I don't go to the cyber bit in the cinema in probably close to 20 years
You know what I mean?
Yeah, they're actually going into a cinema set down and watch the movie. It's been over 20 years for me
Okay, yeah, this song is a Scotty song from the great war if you remember great war
The green one he was born and fought on the western front of the great war I guess Germans
Well, I mean that
The four stuff is, not that, I mean, it's, yeah, I mean, it's like, I just don't know much about it, so I can't really speak on it, but I think I don't like wars in general, I think a lot of them are these stage productions, and the world is already connected and working together.
people are the on to say are you
I was I took a nap yesterday
yesterday for like eight hours or something
so that's a little bit far that you can see my beautiful
you can see one please don't say your
On YouTube to pee in a bucket on the stream and I said oh you don't pee on my stream
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
And then I was like looking I was on the my phone looking at the restaurant
Get a picture up from and then I hear the sound of peeing and then I look and he has the bucket
And he and he you can see he's peeing in the bucket and then
Yeah, and then the mom and then the mom said then the mom said the mom said hey
He said you said porn bomb
And then they said he he's he he's pulled the camera down and he had a small red penis and
It looks like a
People all that many chances
Yeah
You're sitting like up there. You're about to you're gonna start a flash. I know you're not wearing underwear under there. Are you you're not you're not
I just know you're not
Why did why would you film my show without underwear on?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, Casey said he saw your nuts. I don't want to end. Oh, okay guys. Did anybody see that's cuz anybody verify?
I don't I don't see nothing. I don't I don't mean and he's like a cupboard by the thing
No, hey
Yeah
I don't want to see I don't want to see his wiener right now because it's on my stream. I it's like formal. Yeah, so
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
Okay, he was kidding, okay
I just uh, you know, but you know two times and uh, you know, I just I know that he's a good guy because I can see he's like
It's creative
You know entertaining funny character. I'm not like sure why he's like, you know trying to like
You know bomb my show
But I want to take one more chance to find out
Yeah, some people um
Yeah, I've given people more than one chance and regretted it before because they just do it the same, you know
You know how it is. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, I mean I get I'm but I'm really I'm really ridiculous because I mean
There's guy Alex McQueen. I don't know if you know Alex's as like I just went through all this drama back and forth with Alex
And they ever all the chat was there a lot of the chat was like, you know
So fed up with them and he was just like so disrespectful and he was going power crazy and
I went through all this stuff and then I would always defend him. I would always like say, you know, he's a good guy like
I want him around and
Anyway
Yeah, the other night he just went off on me like very like very like um
Like he just attacked me. I mean he never attacked me like he did the other night. He was but he was like
Yeah, and then and so I but it was a shock and the and I've been in the same day beta attack me like like that
And it's like it was like these are so completely different like them away
Yeah
You you you
You give people a lot of chances
You see what this guy's doing this old Elger guy, right? Yeah, pull this tilt up over his knees, right?
You saw that
Oh, did she get up? Can you say can you walk forward?
It's me that's your camera. You're not going to read this your camera. I'm taking you up. No, you're not in there
No, no, no, no, no
I get the feeling he was getting ready to uh, yeah, yeah, because that's what that's what he was
That's what he did before. I don't know if he started like a little justing a little bit little by little
He was like he was like he was sitting up on something and I started pulling back and he's not wearing underwear
uh, he's always he's smiling about it and um
Yeah, I mean if you've done it before and
Before is a pretty good indication
Hello Jim good to see you
Yeah, I mean I've been poor bummed over a hundred times and you know, I'm always I'm pretty good
I just instantly will just mostly I'll delete the stream because you know, even if it's private
I guess people can
People can try to try to strike them with the status that a thing is people will try to form bomb and then they'll like
They'll try to
They strike you or flag you and stuff like that from there what they're doing. It's just like it's just it's like such a dirty
I hope they
Just want to act like children and that's basically the bottom line right plenty of adults. Oh, he's coming back
He said he's good. He said he's just good.
I can put this filter like you here.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, no, no, no.
Can you just sit down on normal chair?
Just sit down on normal chair.
I don't like to be sitting like that.
Like I said, some people, they just want to behave like children.
It makes them feel good.
Yeah, I mean it's like that's like
Like some people like when they build a form bomb that knows they scream out with clear or they're like or they'll say the n-word would take such
like such like excitement or like
Mr. Big Pipe's that do he did he and we're bomb me like he because I wouldn't like to let him back on after a few hours
He and we're bomb me and
And say I that's your show and they take nanananana. Oh, I see you back stage. Oh, yeah, what do you do it?
Okay, you're sitting in a chair. Okay, sit into the chair
I wouldn't bring him up. You see I've had enough already, but it's you panel. No, this is what I found
I had a guy on my panel guy came up. I
Didn't know who he was but he showed himself
Backstage so I let him up. He was a young kid and he started just asking like these weird questions
Don't know even know what he was talking about
So I put him down. I sent him off the panel
He goes into the private chat on the back and he fills it with spam non-stop for like 30 minutes back there
Just spamming the private chat
So eventually I threw him out of the studio
that guy and
But I gave him every chance to stop doing it, but I don't if he thought it would help him get back on the panel or not
By being a jerk
Right when when you when people react negatively to your discipline towards them in my in my view
That's that's a bad sign
Okay, if I tell if I throw someone off or time someone out and they react in a negative way
That makes it less likely that I'm ever gonna tolerate them again. You know
Yeah
Well, okay, so
No, he actually illmatic
I
Yeah, okay. Let me just tell you back stage. Okay, yeah
I will if I if you do a few poor mommy today. Okay, if you do that, okay, I will never ever ever
You'll be banned. Okay. This is I've never I'm done. I'll never you'll never be welcome back
You'll be banned for you forever. Okay
Do not poor mommy
You're seeing a chair, okay
Okay, so
Let's keep it. I
What does that mean in Latin? What is the problem here? Oh, what is the problem here?
No, I think the both is the problem is you come on with underwear in your
You're weird look on your face and box. You've you've
The problem is you come up here and act like an idiot. That's the problem, right?
I'm not going to psyche. Why would I like to ridiculate myself by showing my tiny...
If I had a big cock, it was already on the screen, but Ilya Oblomov has all the European men.
But European cock, you better keep it in your pad.
See how many fans you can say in one sentence.
So we are one of them, very tiny.
Yeah, I'm like even if I'm gay and it's like I'm kind of like getting sick of all the penis talk
I mean, it's like
Well, you know what is the you know, I don't know. It's like it's like everybody's just talking everyone's talking about penis all the day
it's like
No, it's it's it means the cool thing. It's like a
Guy wearing a wig is your first clue. It's not my problem
Sassy's right about that
I'm gonna have to go soon psych after my teeth. Okay. I'm gonna go for I'm gonna go fishing
I'm going out on the Long Island sound fishing for strippers
I'm not
I'll go in like, you know, five or ten minutes. Okay. Don't key. Don't key. You are going to report to your priest
government
because you work for them you drink tea and
It's not my cousins in town for a couple of days. So we're going fishing
Cool
Yeah, I mean I live on redondo Beach pier so I could uh redondo Beach pier. Yeah
Well, I live nearby
I've been down by redondo. I know some people at redondo. I remember the meat puppets used to record
It used to say they all been recorded at redondo beach
Yeah, a lot of things been filmed. Yeah, they've
Baywatch's films here and Baywatch
Pennywise
How many times you have been talking off to Pamela Anderson's pictures?
Baywatch was the most watched show on the planet when it was on TV, right?
The most watched
Yes, but Doki, that was the answer to my question.
Well, yeah, well, I remember I got that video as soon as I heard their Hanim video, I watched that.
I got that on PSS.
The original the original
We kind of the
They got the guy stole it from the safe in this house and they published they put their video on the website
It was one of the first videos they sold on a website
It's over to third part. It's a really just the Pam and Tommy story is really interesting
There was only six thirty in the morning for you
It is six twenty three. Yeah
Yes
Yeah, I did I did I did DMT last night a few times
People my friends brother were GMC pen. Have you ever tried that?
DMC DMT DMT DMT DMT yeah, yeah DMT is ecstasy, right?
No, it's it's actually from a tree bark. It's actually a natural
Yeah, it comes from like a tree bark like a costy tree or
I used to smoke a lot of crack I used to use dope I
Used to take acid a lot, but that was literally 35 years ago. I stopped all that shit when I was like 25
I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I was I
Yeah DMT yeah DMT is just it's not something that I would just go out and use you know
I've had five kids in the meantime don't it can we see your baseman right now
Can you show the baseman where you?
Yes
but DMT is something I know that the kids use today.
Yoki, so awesome, baby.
We want to see.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, Dougie, Dougie, Dougie, Dougie,
it's like amazing, it's like, it was like,
cause I like had, I got it before,
like I was making it and stuff last year,
but it was like the DMC pen,
like it gives you such a big hit,
like that it's like, and it's so powerful that it's like,
I don't think I've had,
I don't think it was,
I've never had it as strong as it was, it was so good.
Yeah, it was just like it's just like it's just like amazing visuals and
Just feel it's amazing
There was fun. So it kind of very energized from that place. I have a very irregular sleepy schedule
I, I, I bet it was the strongest thing that Loki has ever tried is the breast milk from his mother's movies.
That we comb that in the drain when you die?
The breast milk from your mother's movies.
Yeah, it's like when you, when your guy about to die, it like is released,
like people will have these hallucinations or like things.
Being paranoid.
They keep being paranoid paranoid of it. What did I put up in paranoid?
That's making me paranoid
Well, it's a blessing bless they bought me from you we and stuff and I don't know is think
I said I've done this guy for like a long time and now he's like comes in like very like look like flirty and like with
Like almost have to make
Like you can you please change I got keep a little kiss for doggy. Yeah familiarity beans contempt. Oh
do you want any balloons for me can i get a kiss too am i the right way guys no can i get a kiss too
other way there you go that way and a hug i will give you a hug
but it's a friendly hug inside me
like a cold fish okay the other way up
Yeah, thank you. Yeah, okay. I
appreciate your advice.
I'll give you.
Thank you.
You have to be careful. European
packers can't go missing anymore where you live.
We'll see you later. See you later.
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, so you just found my sister
But I don't know no no no wait what?
Okay, but what do you do when that whiskey gets about this much you're gonna start
Here's a lifting your skirt up and turning around
I know it's cool. It's nice. It's very nice.
This is a killed knife. Do you know how to kill the killed knife?
No. It's down here.
I'm sorry. Can we just relax a little bit?
Yes. Small talk, cigar.
Yeah
Yeah, I'm sorry my address went to the little bit and maybe I'll go to the
Forefinding so you have to understand that
Doki and everybody is trying to brainwash you and tell you what to do
You do what is right or wrong in your mind
Yeah, well, yeah, that's what I'm trying to do is in the
You know, but I do like to have but I came here as a friend as you are a monitor from your back down
Matt, okay
Thank you. Okay. I get I get some
Some people that what sort of why I would like to use help so if you can you know, you can help me in any way
You know, you know, you know if you didn't like
Bring people here or you know, like or bring people like an interview or I don't know
Is that is that I thought is that like all the way up the side is that your leg bearer of the site
What's going on? Oh, and you don't hear I say, excuse me. You're good. Okay. Oh
Guys, we have to be careful. I showed his buttocks to good times. Well, but he covered
You showed your butts at good times
Crystal Marie says there you
The Chris he showed his butt here, too. He showed you and he shows yeah, he also shows weiner last time
Actually, I'm thinking, I'm thinking that Ejo would,
oh yeah, there's a fishnet stockings
or like those little garters, those are the good.
Thank you, Chris, I appreciate it.
Yeah, he's done it twice to me, but.
I'm gonna give one more chance, but he's doing like a little Sharon Stone action. I mean, I think eventually it's gonna eventually
I'm gonna like turn my head for half like a minute look for the cat and then
Okay, okay
This song was for you and for everybody. Thank you. I really appreciate it. It's beautiful. I do love a
Scottish music and I love your your kilt and
This camera will say that the object is too small
He's seeing that he promised, he knows it's his last chance, this is like, he can't show his balls again.
Or his balls at all.
But he's, okay, have you ever seen basic instinct, are you replaying the...
Jinjin, Jinjin, everybody, let's drink.
I'm afraid to even turn my head for a second.
Let's see.
You love Christian. I love Christian. But psyche, psyche, please. Only mods. Oh
My gosh, mr. Big Pikes is here
Yeah, that guy
My balls are here and the guilt is so
There is no right here
I think he's like I think I see anything. Okay. Okay. I don't care. I think he like is is that imitating
Like me because it's like I think it's his voice
I think because he's like you completely different state. He had a California accent
But it's like a not like a really bad California accent like not a real one. He's an exaggerated one
That's like it's like like on that Saturday at live the Californians
It's like that kind of accent and that's what he and then he was like doing it like really really
It's like, it's like, it's like,
it's like, I don't mean that this is no voice.
He just talks like that, imitating me, I think.
I don't know.
What do you think guys?
Have you heard him talk that way, other places?
He just talks like that and he's like,
he talks like this.
And then he's like, he's like,
he's like, he's like, he's like,
he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like,
he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like,
How's everyone in a chat doing? You know guys, you know, you know, you're not a mod you're still able to use the nightbot command
You'd always help me out
Or just asking you think even if you say I'd like to stream or something like that. I would love that one
And as you know, I don't know I just I don't think I'll really have a
desire to add
Oh there yeah
Mr. Big five years and he oh, I just can tell he's up to now
It seems then also people will get like mad. They'll be mad at you and you won't even know and
Then and then they'll come in like is it so they'll come and attack you
Like he's like he came back mad when I took him off for like a few hours or something like that or he was like
Mikey I have long years. Oh
Oh, here we go. Oh, he's back again
Christine can you come up on channel? Can you come up?
Amanda if you can or if you want to in or anybody wants to come up like
This hat with some people
That's your chance to talk to it. Yeah, I kind of like I might have lost for words with you guys
I'm afraid to ask a question, but I'm afraid
If I say the wrong thing his first gonna come up
There's not gonna be
Underwear under them, and I have to end the stream. I mean, it's like it's okay if I do it's only been an hour
It's just I don't like I don't like to continually have to I
Don't know if it's good for the algorithm to complete the keep starting and restarting streams, then you lose out
Yeah, you can't go right now. It's okay. No, it's okay
It is
I feel like I left alone with these creepy, creepy guys.
What underwear? Do you want to see underwear?
I want to see it.
Saiki, what are you talking?
I can't see anything.
I know I'm not saying that. I'm saying I just feel like I'm alone in a room with you
and I'd rather have other people here.
Why do you always think like that Saiki?
I'm certainly not
It's very small
Now it's very cold here. So it's very tiny
Yeah, well
I'm not I'm not really interested in your weir
Keep it. Keep it under wraps
I want to see a
Upskirt killed video. I'll go to
for hug
So I hate when he puts his hands behind his head like that.
Oh, yeah.
That's like, is that like a, are you making a Masonic?
Are you making a Masonic right now?
No, I'm not making a Masonic.
Are you making a Masonic just for that me?
Look, I'm drinking the whiskey.
Scotch whiskey.
Scotch whiskey, OK.
I may wait until you start, he will expose himself.
He better not, he'll never be on the show again.
But it's worth it for me to give him a chance.
Oh, oh, oh.
Why I can't be relaxed?
Because you're gonna accidentally fall back in your chair,
and then you're gonna say, oh, I was actually fell,
but you're, in the summer side, fell backwards like.
My back.
You'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do it, you'll do
No, I don't trust you
You said you wouldn't do it and the last time I made you promise you weren't and I told you not to pee in the bucket
I was like don't pee in the bucket as if you're not being a buck. I was a little bit when I said I
Said I said go on asking me. Oh, I was saying nothing. I was just stretching a little bit. Okay. I said go I said go off
Go off camera
I picked up my phone for like one second
ja olen kuulunut.
Ja sitten
olen tullut nähdä
sinua, mutta
minä olen tullut
minulla, mutta...
Psyki!
Mikä olet pysynyt?
Psyki, olet pysynyt?
Minä olen pysynyt pysynyt pysynyt
ja minä olen pysynyt
Yeah, Mr. Big Pipe says like that
He's just like harassing me taking our studio. He's using that he's like
He's a but yesterday don't mean shit. We are leaving now right here
We have to be
He was he was in the base in the back. She had counting problems. Let's see the absent need hands
No, he can pee. He can pee in the bucket, but I said, do it on my show. And I said, do it on my show, right?
No, no, no, do it off my show. You know, he said he would do it off my show. He said, do it off my show.
And he does it on my show.
Everyone, he said, yeah.
And but why is everyone why now why is everyone peeing and like and like jars buckets and like
A man or are you a chicken you are not a chicken?
Okay
Yeah
Lady Esma and her word is well
Gosh, yeah, oh so anyway
Please don't show your picture. It looks like you're like, why do you keep smiling like that?
The thing is psyche the problem if your chat sometimes sees that they have no
Only thing that they just want to go with you. We are talking right here, right?
So it's wonderful to be with you
psyche I'm here
No, sir. Oh, no sir. Oh, will
Um, yeah, I don't understand these accusations. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
As human beings, we go through brainwashing from.
Can I make scotis?
Do you have any scotis viewers?
Do you know what he's saying?
I'm not sure.
Who is from Scotland here on the chat? Nobody is from Scotland.
I am from Europe and I love all you American people.
I represent Vladimirovich Putin, the most democratic president in the world.
Mä oon vain täällä PIS-toksen russian federaation ja USA.
Mutta onko siellä joku, joka on kautta kautta?
Ei.
Ei kautta.
Mä oon amerikin, mutta...
Kun siellä on kautta kautta kautta,
mä haluan tehdä kautta.
Well, like I said, I have a lot of ancestry from there, but
Never been I've been to a moment in England. Let's see
I'm doing nothing. I'm doing
You're being very doing the very dangerous territory right now
you are 33 people in chat. Hello, everybody.
Like nobody wants to see my tiny pecker. Relax now, a little bit. Okay. Relax.
I don't know. Nobody wants to see it, but it doesn't even show it. I mean,
Yeah, that's a new jacket. Oh, I don't know. So, uh, Monro, of course, I
Don't think psyche. I have to ask you that the sex simple as
Jimmy was talking about this modern Monroe. It's interesting that
Minulla oli ennen ja yksinkertaisu, joten minulla only sellaista maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman maailman
Have you seen that movie, something like it?
Yes, Tony Curtis, Marilyn Monroe, actually, I was in a school.
Manny Monroe was starring in that movie, and after that I understood.
Okay, she was like, yes.
I was, yeah, I was in a, oh yeah, do you think she was trans?
Well, I was in a school play that, not a school play, it was like a community theater play.
It was called Sugar, and it was based on something like it.
I watched the, I was in the play and I watched that movie.
It's a really good movie.
Okay, okay, okay.
It was a really good movie though.
It's Tony Curtis.
It's a really good movie.
And Marilyn Monroe.
Yeah.
I think he attended a full festival.
He was an old man.
He was wearing a suit.
Come on, there is so many women, but all these corrupted politicians, you know,
why they are hunting like one piece of meat, like, tell me honestly, who killed her?
What do you think? Who is behind that, her assassination?
J.F.K., sinä olet sanoittanut, mitkä tehtäisivät?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey
I mean, it's like it's just not that's not how it's not the story of Camilla. Yeah, that's not the jfq story
That sounds like a porno porno scripts. Okay, so let's be a little bit
More classy. Okay. Okay. Mr. Big Five. Wait, wait, wait. Oh my gosh
Ilya is more like a respite comedian. Oh
Well, you know, that was just profanity who's just saying the you know, the Kennedy family
was in
Weird sexual position. I mean, it's like fun. Stop it
inappropriate
Let's see. I don't know how's everyone doing in chat like, you know, is the I don't know a lot of you might be
Near the chat or might be some of my fans
Let me know if you're a fan or not. Let's let me know if you hate me like I'd like I'd like to get a good feel of that
People are feeling me honest, you know, it's uh, like
He is yeah, okay, so I like I like it. Oh, okay. Why is he you're crossing your legs? Okay. Yeah, it gives the kids
You know, so it's like basically
one little
No, you're just
Guys
Okay, thank goodness
What won't say we've a guest it's just me
Okay
I'm gonna tell you get down and sit in a chair like a normal human being
Nobody's giving you the attention you want today sit down
You're up here not because you care about psych or his channel. You're up here tempting and trying to antagonize
That's all you're doing. Why?
That is a very serious
Accusation well, I don't really care if it's a very serious accusation. I'm speaking the truth
He does you do this every time you come up to him. Why?
This is my third why why can't you not sit? Why can't you not sit in a chair like a normal person?
This is a chair. This is a chair. Sit your, sit your heiny on the seat, not on the back.
There you go. Okay, Mr. Psych, how are you this morning? Good, how are you this morning?
Fine, you just got to act for these grown-ass men that don't know how to behave like children
Yeah
Because I care about mr. Psyche and
I feel what you do
Especially right now
Stressing him that he doesn't need because he is a very nice gentleman where I'm not so nice
Christine. Yes. I have a one question for you. Can I ask this question? No, because I've asked you numerous questions and you never answer me.
Which questions? Why do you wear a wig and sunglasses in your home? With drapes, curtains or whatever it is, shades closed. Make that make sense.
You don't want to show your real identity
Christie why are you afraid of who you are care about? Why are you afraid of who you are?
Christie is your bad pipe away
Here is that why do you care so much what other people are? I just explained to you why I
Just explained to you why?
I explained to you why, because you, this is not your panel, this is Mr. Sykes, you are not respecting him and he deserves that, now doesn't he?
Are you, are you making this decision on the behalf of Sykes?
Yes I am.
I
Have sat down there long enough watching you again. Why don't you answer my questions? Why do you have a
See see how you are why do you wear wig and sunglasses?
In a home with the shades closed you can see the shades are even closed. Why?
And it's like he's not across the world because it would be dark there
Yeah
Are you to ask me questions
Mr. Bagpipes
Can we just have a little bit
whiskey here and relax?
I have a great idea.
How about you be who you are
instead of pretending who you are not?
Let's start from that you come up.
No, let's start with me sitting in chat.
You sitting on a chair inappropriately in a skill in a kilt with no underwear on
With a wig and glasses you tell me that's not suspicious get out of here
Who are you to tell me?
What to do?
I'm definitely not your mother because my sons
Grown men don't act like you do
But Christine, so do you take care of your sons instead of arguing with nobody on the internet?
I don't argue with my sons.
No, but why you are arguing with me? Take care of your sons. Perhaps they need some...
You know what? My sons, my sons are men and they are all at work.
This is the bigger you say Christie something. It's okay. I'm done arguing with you
You are because you are telling me what to do and then yeah
I am because I cannot wait until you expose yourself and he blocks you forever
And I will remind him about blocking and banning you. I will remind him
What are you doing here? I will remind him
Yes, but he will you don't want none of this, right? Mr. Psyche
He can power you this morning Psyche me
But Christy, this is let the adults talk now Ilja
I know he's going to
I would like to massage your shoulders a little bit, you know, don't you touch me with those perverted hands?
Yes, and then I would have just you wouldn't touch me. You're not man enough to touch a woman
I'm sorry. I failed. Oh you failed yourself. I hate to break that news to you
You failed yourself one
Good then I guess you have to take the glasses off and then the wig will fall off and then you'll then you'll have to expose
Who you really truly are?
Fake accent, fake clothes, fake places
Eric, he's not a creating
Kristina why you are spending so much time for all this pussy? This is the internet, come on
Why do you? Oh, I know why you do because you're an alcoholic with nothing else to do
What else?
What else you know about my life. I'm
Mr. Fake pervert I am going to mute up, but I'm gonna stay up here
I'll just wait for your little hand. Oh, sorry psych. I didn't mean to do it. I won't do it again routine
Now you are so mean
Kristiina, en haluatko sinä, Kristiina, oletko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko haluatko
She is a perfect person to live there with I think that's a dog
She lives with but this is internet. We have to relax talk and don't stop
But thank you. First of all, I never have said anything bad to you, right? I think that is right. I
Hate nobody here
Mr. Ilja, actions speak a lot louder than words and your actions on here have been very bit poor choices.
I'm surprised because I thought Kristina.
Had a life or something but instead she's a spine what Ilya I do I do have a life
but my grandchildren my grandchildren are coming next week and I am
Surprising them with a nice trip
So I've decided to spend the day with a travel agent to find something fun to do
Kristi, voin sanoa jotain, että ei ole mitään kertaa sitä, koska asioista on niin hienoa.
No niin, ettei minä olen, ettei minä olen, ettei minä olen, ettei minä olen, ettei minä olen.
I don't know that if you do that. It's your job. You know, um, trust me
Hey, almost everybody here knows me. Never done it. Never will. I don't need that because I'm very satisfied in life
Yes, but internet and real life are two different things. You have to well, you know, that's you're right
They're two different worlds
Um, they do sometimes they do sometimes meet those two different worlds
And just because it's the internet does not mean we can act like adults
We can still act like adults and be in the internet world
Just saying
Yeah, how about you go find another room to hang in
instead of telling people to take a long walk off a short pier.
What's not a threat? Oh my god, I have to report you to FBI.
Oh, are you threatening to report the channel? Is that what you're doing?
No, I'm going to report to you to the FBI, that something will happen.
Oh, I think you ought to do it to the CIA, report me to the CIA, go ahead, or Interpol.
I think Interpol, report me to Interpol.
See if that works.
No, they already said it that, you know.
I'm Christian I don't hate you come on relax
Okay, um, mr. Sight do you want to handle mr. Doug D since I've
Graciously come up here to handle Ilza
Okay, well I handle him you
Yes, I'd like you to handle him if he doesn't know how to behave he can go find something to do
Okay, yeah, he's not going to harass me in chat
And see I had I the only reason I can see him is because I am up here
Yeah, I mean it's the guy about your night go I know well because you know I
So yeah, that's one of the DMC and stuff and so I was like it's like they're just like a kind of crazy couple and
you know
They're running around doing stuff as the
She's like she cleaned my whole kitchen like it's like the floor is like beautiful. It's like so
Maybe she's coming my house. I need somebody to come clean my floors
Well, it's very it was very nice of her and so it was very it's a pretty cool night
And as we just hung out and like watch music videos and there are you know, the TMC and and
It was fun hanging out with people in the real world
I don't do it too often. Well, you probably need to do it a little bit more
Please I'm on the we're ignoring you Ilja. We're at the let the adults talk here. Okay
No, there's a man down never more that's adult. Let the adults talk. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There's no
month. There's no month to my chef. There's no month. I'm the only month or the night part is the
only month or why these women, these old women, they are ruining everything for good fun.
We can have good fun here because apparently there seems to be more more
Normal women and perverted men on social media. I still haven't figured that out yet, but that's my constitution
Channel we need to this kind of
No, no psyche. Did you forget psyche invited me up? Did he invite you up?
Yeah, Psyche always says that although hot men can always join to me well see
Mr. Psyche is trying to change his channel view a little bit and
He's trying to get more of us normal people in
And I'm not sure you're fitting that though
But that's okay because because the ones that don't belong here are slowly weeding themselves out
Bagpipes make him sing the rocket man. Hey, we can do like a karaoke here. Have you not realized
Sight does not want his channel the way it used to be
We are going to do readings. We're going to have adult conversations. We're going to do more tarot
We're going to let people speak maybe on
Their supernatural experiences or their beliefs then I mean those are things we're looking at and in a world of turmoil
Those are kind of probably good things to be hearing and talking about to get our mind off the everyday thing that's going on in this world
that was very f**king boring, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye
beautiful man, attractive man, and we can talk about men stuff.
If you're wearing underwear and you weren't like, you know, teasing me with like pulling
if you're tilted a bit and then saying some off the ball shit.
I don't know, like sometimes I don't think I know what's going on in the conversation.
I don't know where you're from. I don't know who I think it's like you're everything is bad
I don't know
Okay, but why are you why are you Irish today once you rush in last weekend, right?
Don't think Russians wear kilts. It's goddess goddess. I'm sorry. I know. Yeah. Yeah
Because there's light coming in that shade there
Koska minulla on tämä puolesta tämä label 5, se on skottelat ja minulla on vaikea ottaa jatkuu.
Well, you know, you can buy that label. A lot of different places.
Label 5 on skottelat.
He know might be big. I'm always famous.
All these American viewers here, I'm not comparing Europe or America.
Difference to me
Nobody believes you. You know that it'll do, right?
And that's that's all I I come with peace. I like the whole the chat all this
That's why I wear this skill I bought from Scotland
Well, take your take your wig off and your glasses off in a home where you've got shades pulled down
It's very simple
You only come up, Christine, and saw that your troll.
Do you have a little troll? Do you know?
What?
In your legs.
You saw?
What did you tell me to do?
I don't know what that is.
Go ahead and sit back and relax, sit in your chair relax, my goodness, you look so tense.
You'll be fine.
I'm not looking for any problems, but why are you attacking me?
I have never said nothing against you.
Much better, isn't it?
You're looking way too tense.
And you know if somebody like him's gonna stop it you can't you can't prevent it if you let him up you can't prevent it
So if it happens it happens
Yeah
Right
Fine he's fine
Okay
Trust me, you know sake you're probably the only one in this community that lets him up anymore. You know that right?
Careful Marty Miguel
He's he's just itching here. Don't put your leg up. Don't put your leg up. Don't do it
Okay
Why would I solve my tiny pecker? It's a europea pecker.
Well, you've done it before. I mean, why'd you do it before?
Are you playing the same record like this one?
You did it before. What makes you think you won't do it now?
Trust is built. You have broken that trust over and over and over.
I think that's like a counter. Oh, that's a FBI.
Oh yes, now I understand.
FBI, yes. Do a crime that I can charge you.
Okay, now I understand this, all the woman.
He is working from all of this agency who is against the Russia.
I work for two agencies in Interpol.
I work for Interpol too.
Kristine, I have to tell you something that if you are a police officer or something,
but while you are not, that's a crime.
You have to remember that.
I work for Interpol.
Oh, everyone was excited to talk back to the police officer, but it's okay. We're good. We're good. You're good, Ilja. We got this.
So, okay, so we don't have to report and ask you who is this dog woman from?
Lava, you think he's Iranian? No, Iranians blacked out. They don't get any TV, any satellite today.
And it's dark and they over there too are almost dark
But anyways, anyways, what do you want from me or this?
I mean, do you want attention?
You know, I don't care about America woman because you know I can go to America
No, are you flirting with me? You're in America because it would be like
I've been midnight in Europe right now.
It'd be dark in Europe.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, it's dark.
And there's daylight peeking through your blind there.
Yeah.
It looks like it's early morning,
so it's probably West Coastish.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yeah.
It's probably but it's like it looks like it's kind of almost the weather like outside like here
West coast what if you what if you is like
like nearby or
Probably your neighbor playing you. Oh
My gosh, that was my name. I was my name. Oh my gosh
Hey, Harry. Good morning
Hey, how are you Mikey Mike? I look like I look like I look like foxy
I'm a big nose. I have floppy ears and I'm all soft and cuddly
And I should go find a wig and sunglasses shit night
But I don't even admit that you I mean he says it's his real hair. So I mean he won't even tell us
That's not a real hair. I
Mean he never he he won't pull it. He won't he won't show that it is
Okay, hope if you won't pull it
He's hugged the brace up very lightly
Oh, yeah, wait, why is your hand down by the edge of your skirt, right?
Saiki, I love you so much, honey. We love you too much, but we are talking about me, you know.
We can talk something else. Why are you talking about me?
We try talking about other things and you keep bringing it back to you.
Well, I mean I don't know to ask you because you'll lie, any answer you'll, yeah, yeah, any question I can ask you'll lie, give you a elaborate story though, it was a waste of my time, I just don't know what to ask.
See, I think, see here's the thing, Elja, psyche is tired of the fake people and the lies.
I mean, you can have like a like, you know, you know where this guy is, but you can at least like
Yourself or like you'd be real. I mean, it's like, I know it may mean is like but it's like it's like, you know
There's like it's like hanging out with like a Disney
Theme park, you know whether one of the actors in the theme park in the costume
It's like it's really hard to communicate. They're uncomfortable being in the costume
And you can't do very much, like with, people won't be weird to their walk around with a Disney character, I don't know.
I haven't said you did. I mean, you pull around me twice.
Yeah, and I think it was three times and then he did the pain in the bottle thing shown as penis. Oh my god
Well, nobody did I mean, I would mean I would mind
Seeing it was on my stream and I
Know Mikey, that's me
That's when I clean up. I actually put makeup on sometimes.
It's gonna be a hot, hot day. Yeah. What am I talking about? It's beginning in the summer in Florida.
Every day is going to be a hot, hot day. Yep. Get ready for this. Yeah. It's gonna be a cool summer, right?
Is that true?
Well, what's up? I gave up cool summers 20 years ago when I left Minnesota
No more cool summer since then
It was pretty nice here though. It should be pretty nice
You're a lot of time. It doesn't get way too high California. You know, especially by the ocean. There's no ocean breeze
Well, I'm by the ocean
Yeah
But they still get to keep the humidity in the storms.
We have storms every day, about three o'clock.
Every day.
They only sometimes only last 15 minutes
and then it makes the weather so much worse.
I mean, I've met a ton of people from Florida recently
like on a forecast and stuff like,
and find different streamers,
like I found a lot of Florida streamers interesting.
And of course I'd live like,
you know, I'd love to go to Florida to see at least about.
you know, I think, I think, too, I think, too crazy right now, like, um, with the, like, her chat was the, I don't know, people from my chat would, I would say, go to her chat, and then we'd all go to her chat, and then they would start trolling, either trolling her or trolling me and stuff in her chat, and like, then taking credit for trolling her.
Oh, that's social media. We all troll.
Yeah.
Yeah, that is the way it is.
Now he's making me know.
I have this here.
It doesn't give it to him.
Yes.
So it's the case.
But you're ill just.
See, here's the thing.
Let me explain.
He's putting that there just in case
because he can't control himself.
Isn't that just the weirdest thing, he has to control himself, he has no control.
Before I don't remember because I always remember your kind of voice like this
In on panel many times together. I was on panel the night you peed in the bottle
Wow, what are you are always complaining? Why can't you just?
Cuz I can cuz I can
See here's the difference at least I admit what I can and can't do unlike you
It's just the etching
Yeah
But anyways excuse me cause I'm disturbing this hot weather. Yes, it's getting
Okay, okay. Yeah
Okay, you gotta go. Oh, yeah, or you're serious. Okay. You're hot. Well, why are you wearing so many clothes if it's hot?
I mean, it's like I'm not telling you take off your clothes and say you can at least say put on underwear and just have a shirt
And you're in your underwear. I think that's fine
See less or even the shirtless if you just want to wear
I
Sun yesterday went cutter lawn all day well not all day, but it took a while to cut the lawn because I had like a half acre
a little over half acre and
He came in showered and put a sweatshirt on and kept the sweatshirt on all day
And I'm like, why do you have a sweatshirt? And he goes it's kind of cold in here. I'm like, oh my god
Se oli kyllä 100° ulos ja hän oli yksinkertaisu.
Kutsutaan.
Tämä oli kysyä, että olin vain katsomaan.
Tiedän, että minun pitäisi sanoa tämä Tom-star.
Hei, hei, hei, hei.
Tällä päivällä päivällä, Ili-Aubulmo oli hyvä.
In the boat, you always need to have this kind of...
Ahhhh!
I don't think you should be playing with the fire extinguisher.
Have you checked the expiration date? Is it still good or has it expired?
You should get a new one every time you change your smoke detector batteries once a year.
Christine!
Esimerkiksi, mutta tämä oli tosiaan.
Ja joka vuotta voitte lähteä tämän erilaisuuteen,
johon heikki nähneet,
tämä fire extinguiser.
Oh, minun erilaisuuteen.
Fire extinguiser.
So they check the pressure that when the fire comes that they're comes out of something, right?
Have you ever had a fire in your home?
I get why you are I try to irritate me you're
Yeah, yeah, how many how many years?
Yeah, how many years since you change that that fire extinguisher fluid
How how old is that fire?
Two months. Oh, it's just too much. Okay. It's
5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5 years, 5
That's why he keeps his blinds closed so that they can stay away from son. Hey Katrina. Good morning
Christine you don't have to always insult me what have I done to you about it? You are not out to more thing any
anyone here
Christine
That's a title song you know
I mean you are insulting someone
I don't I don't I don't there's no way to win. I mean, there's no way to win. How do you win?
How how do I win with you? What is the what is the what would the prize be like, you know, you take up the way?
I mean that would be a maybe a win, but
Yeah
There's no way to win
Chris good mornings
I hope you understand. Excuse me. You were asking something. This is not big. It's not real.
You can ask Chris. Chris K has seen me. First time I've ever been online.
Chris K from Las Vegas. Oh, I know I met Chris in the chat. Hey, Leo. Good morning. Yeah, okay. This is a buster
He's the buster, you know
Christina, but oh
It's quite heavy this one
Hi camera XM Bureau. That's kids names for sure. Hi, Chris
Hi guys
one of us
Mm-hmm
You can never I mean you can be out smart me, but I can never leave it, you know
You have to
Yeah, as far as I mean, what is it? What is it? As far as like, what, like, just like, uh, to get him out the form? Well, I don't know.
That's like, it's the only thing I want out of this nonsense. It's not just fucking shit with balls.
Okay, Dave. Hi. Hi, Mr. Tricks.
Hello, Torex. Good morning, Torex.
Come on, Torex is showing loves.
How about a tarot reading this morning? Sure
I think I'm going to take them kayaking. I taught them how to kayak last summer and the summer before
I'm going to take them I think kayaking
You should do that Christine. You are not a bad person. Maybe you know something about life. I don't know but...
You are
Christie you don't have a personality, you know
You're right. I don't have a personality. I don't have a life. I don't have a job
I don't have a home. I don't have kids. I don't have any of those things
Hmm it's all about the projection. It's such a weirdo
Okay. Okay. I have some, I have some cars. Okay. So, it's very nice to join. You know, have a good day. You know, we are drinking.
Okay. So, there we have, this is the pool car. Alice has the pool. This is Alice, like, you know, looking, following the white rabbit.
and going on a new adventure and
starting something new, but there's like a lot.
It's like, uh, there's a lot unseen.
It's like, as you're going in with the
innocent beginner's blind.
And then you are this like, uh,
you are this queen of flowers.
Okay.
Where's the flowers?
There's a vase in that flower.
Look, there's a fade.
Two eyes and a nose.
That is the beautiful rose is this is the queen of flowers. I think the number of the flowers are gonna be
Flowers are gonna be the ones. Okay, and so the queen of wands
The queen of flowers is a social person
Who it takes pride in her appearance and speaks her minds with elegance and authority?
Admired by others
She commands attention to wherever she goes.
All right.
If it's time to build your, hold your head up high, push your...
Push your
Enviable talents and skills in this way and enhance the unique traits that make you who you are
And so I that really I really do believe that it's you
It's like in this like you and even like this in this even this even this journey might be currently going straight to there
You know, it's like or even you know deeper into your into your queen energy
We do have this five of five of spears. Okay, so the five of so this is the five of swords
So this is like but it's like, you know with like the queen position can come a lot of conflicts sometimes
And so that there's gonna still be the conflict there
It says whether you're locked in conflict with the tempestuous queen of hearts or frustrated by a misunderstanding
and your communication with the mad hatter
The five of spears is known as the ultimate conflict card
Wherever battle you find yourself in know that now isn't the time to back down. You've been
You'll have to be creative and determined to gain the advantage
Well, that's kind of psyche. I have to tell you I am
in this situation right now
What do you just read to me? Oh, you are key down. Yeah, you know
Check it. I have to tell you that I have over two brain cells, you know, I have a big head
two brain cells
but you know
Disturbed people like me, you know, they are
Okay, perhaps I will back down. Yeah
I
Give it the time a little bit. Okay. It's like you guys say more like you got to know when to hold them know when to hold them
Have the song go for scene you got to know
No, when to follow them
No way to run no way to hide
Okay
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, you don't want to back down unless you know, you absolutely
You absolutely absolutely have to but you know, but I would say it's a good fight
It might be all three
It's a terror. Oh, thank you. Awakens or hyphers
hit
Hi smash is a piper's fit. Well, okay. You can now is like this is a miss a big miss a big pipes or mister
Is it up? What's up? What's going really itching? Look at that smirk
Merck. Oh
It's a skirt. It's a skirt. Look at this. Okay. Somebody who wears a tilt does not call it a skirt
You see what he's doing? Okay, that's enough
Yeah, that's enough
That's enough
Don't you understand it's a cute you can't see nothing. It's a dark place. You're not wearing underwear. No, he's not
Why are you not here and your legs are open in front of the camera
I am not going to say he's going to he's going to uncross when he lifts it up and says it was an accident so that you don't
ban him. Yeah, you are. You always say it's an accident.
But it's been an hour that he's been playing. Good morning, Marcy. You come up, Marcy. Easy. You come up. We're just hanging.
Cat mother or whatever, you know cat mothers
I'm a cat I'm a cat father here. Hey Tracey Tracey
She's a day with me. Hi, babe. Come on in toy apps. There we go
Let's see
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my
All right, let me go to the service
We got a great chat. Yeah, we have kind of pretty good chat throughout the day
It's better when another person comes up because it makes him smaller, so if he does it, it's not as much as a risk.
Like all these, you know, these middle-aged, cat women, you know, they're doing everything, you know, that's cute.
You have a free chat, you know, just keep it going.
So Christy you do is just
Here I'm talking on nobody but yet you are attacking me my personality my
my beloved
You know presents
Here in the American community. Sorry that was my son's motorcycle
Yeah, he decided it was a nice day today. So he finishes work early. Nobody cares about you are any fucking
Money do you care about my life?
Thank you
The only one who doesn't
But like you all these one mothers they always say they sound like the same, you know
always widen do this do that you know this is wrong this is why we're we're the one you
sound one
doesn't think I it's like you know it's a good a good conversation
what do nothing okay where you're on your knees on your bed what and it kills
Why are you on your knees on your bed on a kilt and it kills? Oh, it's a chair
Okay, okay
Remember I told him the sit is heiny on the seat of the chair instead of the back of the chair. Yeah
Okay, there's many fortune here
so that looks pretty outside
anything to get the camera off of the
there you go
right
oh honey, honey nice
yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, so you have a good message or like, you know, or uh, you know
What brings you to the panel like you really haven't like
Said very much, you know, I mean you said a lot but they haven't said anything at all really
Say something
Oh
Yeah, no, I just want to chill here or relax. Okay
I'm afraid I'll trigger him. I don't know. Okay. I'm trying to figure out what type of trip. Do we want?
Do we want
nice hotels? Do we want a theme park?
We want the keys. Oh
Be Keenies. Yes, we want be Keenies. Yes
A little bit with the baby oil and everything like that, you know some cream
That's what we want here
My goodness
Nothing in the back
Oh mr. Oh mr. Big pipes. Oh my god. What do you say?
So what is that? Yeah, he said block me on YouTube pussy dork. So I'm not trying to chill
Hexing you dork
You are cursed of me now cursed motherfucker
Hex hex hex
666 the dark is terrified of me. Just trying to chill. What's what WTF?
Terrified dork afraid of chilling. I'm just trying to chill
Literally trying to chill the lady is jelly SF. I'm the real deal lady
That's what he said
Yeah, see I knew it because it's like people were saying oh his
his
his avatar on his screen is a
chaos magic symbol and
You know, these are different
Magical
Magical symbols made and you know different shapes and things there's different ones different shapes and different traditions
But in chaos magic, it was like though it was pretty big in the 70s
You know, it's still probably popular today, but in a, these, and these shapes can't, and he kept trying to come on the panel
And he should show it. This, this shape was all on the screen. It looks, I thought it was like a logo for a computer company
But it's like, it's just like, and people are using these magical symbols and it's like, so I, I had a feeling he was like, and then he said
There's a lot of insane Satanists running around and I used to be, you know, I used to be in the Church of Satan and
And I think I just understood that
They, the agenda is very dark and it's like it's kind of it's not
It's not a place of love. It's like a place of like
Dehumanizing and like
It's looking at humans as animals and themselves as gods and basically doing bringing doing evil and increasing evil
Cutting up humans from the divine source and so, you know, they get from themselves
So
Valities yes, but the value of the power forms
Yeah, you can see how this let's say I'll any weapon if formerly gets me so not prosper, you know
I don't know, they posted something about principalities and powers, that's the war we
fight not against flesh and blood, but against the powers, principalities, etc.
These structures, the spiritual powers, the spiritual powers too.
I
Think he got stunted in his maturity back there
Yeah, well, you know I have
Everybody everybody has
Their own their own trauma that happened in their life their own
Experiences make them the way they are and
you know
Yeah, I have I have empathy for people
But I believe that people can always change for the better and it's like we can always strive to go to our higher side
North no, that's why we're here on earth is actually have time to improve and to and to change ourselves and so
We all have trauma, I don't care who you are every human in the world who's had some type of trauma
Here's the difference
Want you
Come to realization of what their trauma was and it's not going to hold you down anymore
That's where you
Present to launch further in life. If you don't ever come to terms with that trauma
You failed the launch and there's never a maturity
Yeah, and that's like it's a part of it is a is a yo
Very boring because you know after all being a human is that
survival, and you have to have a little bit of narcissistic behavior to survive in the
world. Otherwise, you will be dead. That's my opinion.
No, I agree. I mean, I agree, but what about you, Christian?
I think you know why if you are so stuff, you know, it was like narcissism is a spectrum too. And I think it's like a big spectrum
where it's like, yes, you are nature. I'm talking about nature. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. And so it's like, you know, like most people are like, you need a little bit of narcissism or else you'll have no self esteem.
You won't feel worthy of it even going outside or, you know, you'll feel ugly. You'll feel
you know but it's like people can be brought to these states no matter what you look like
you will get down with everybody you know it's a last man survive and at this point of this
fucking life it's different than 20 years ago 20 years ago the life everything was different
but now it's a fucking it's cruel
Esimerkiksi, että kaikki nämä järjestäjät, kaikki nämä järjestäjät, hei, olen järjestäjät,
en tiedä, mitä se on, mutta kaikki nämä järjestäjät,
olet, että se on järjestäjät.
Se on tosiaan, miten sanoit, se on tosiaan.
Se on tosiaan, kyllä.
Kyllä, tämä on järjestäjät nyt.
In my opinion, that's my opinion, I'm telling you what do you think?
You know, I mean, it's like, you know, kind of like similar to 1984, which was like written,
1984 was written way back in the 50s I think, but it like predicted so many things correctly
about how the world was changed to, you know, the big brother, they have the
You know obey obey obey, you know, all that stuff is coming out now
it's like
It would like us to be more easily controlled eventually
No, that's not easy that's that's yeah
They're just buying their troll on leather
But we failed in my opinion we failed the younger generations
For oh, yeah, look at you. Look at your dress. It's your way
That we failed now. We didn't look at the way you were dressed. This is why you claim that
How can you claim we failed them when you're dressed like that?
What do you mean how do I dress how it has anything to do with that?
En ymmärtää.
Minulla on ollut Skiutlan ja tämä on vain semmoinen.
Skiutlan.
Minulla on kokeiltu.
Täällä on kokeiltu.
Miten olet ollut?
Seuraavaa kautta tai
tämä riklainen puolesta.
Ne tarvitaan kokeiltuja.
Ja oho.
Minulla on kokeiltu.
Ilyoblomoo on kokeiltu.
I didn't fail. I did not. I did not fail. I can take the
I don't mind anything about it, but I think it tells more
about you. We failed the younger generations for all this
bullshit. When you know, and some people feel our parents
failed us and some people feel their parents failed them.
More competition, everything, you know, it's so hard for these younger generations these days.
It is very hard for them.
What's hard?
Everything, competition, everything.
Back in the day, they wasn't like this.
It wasn't a competition who is the best who does this or who does there's always been
Like a good man there's always been competition
Way back in time there's been competition and jealousy go back to biblical times it was even there
Yeah
There are much I mean there was
It was much more brutal
He's the he's getting to the mr. Big Pipe's cast here through it right now
So are you mr. Big Pipe's in a week? Oh come on now
Mr. Big Bagpipes doesn't have enough
stamina to continue with the charade.
I think it's a combination of being
hard on the government and
how-towing on too many things.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that the political
correctness is like, it's all meant to
push people to say that
To the other side like I'm a big back backlash or even a political correctness or even like, you know
I mean
remember remember the dragon how controversial like there was a drag queen that read I guess like a book to like school
and
And and then it's in the people are like, oh my god. Look at it. Look what the trans are doing big drag queens don't even trans they're like
They're uh they're like entertainers. Hey, what is that? What is that? What is that? I'm Elia. Is that a crush? What is that?
What is that? What'd you bring over?
I don't think you can hear me. What is that?
A pipe. What are you doing? A pipe. A pipe? Okay, pipe.
Okay, I've got a pipe. You don't smoke a pipe. No.
Is it a corn cob pipe?
Now it's from the real wood from our you know, how they make this real wood. Okay, so it's a wood pipe
Yeah
Yeah, Christina. Oh, no, come on. That's not a very nice person. No
But harass me
Yeah. Sorry.
Nobody cares about anything interesting because you have been so hard.
Oh, I'm hard.
Man, you have to be...
It's hard.
Just hard.
Yeah.
My goodness, just how should this work?
No, it's right.
Women, right?
You never...
I don't know sometimes you lose, sometimes you win, so I'm glad I'm winning.
Okay, I really need somebody to come put this chair together.
Dressed in a style of a school mom a parent found out she was a man through a fit
Started all the bullshit. I'll do tq people are
So evil and out to kill or you know blank moral or the morals. Yeah, I know I think but it's it's always
Some places worse than other places with that and it's like there's
You know, there's certain certain places. They're okay, but there's nothing coming. I'm in South Bay Los Angeles
There's one gay bar in this whole in the whole city if they're gonna say kind of like
I don't think it's too far away, but it's just the whole city. There's one bar
And the whole three actually three cities, so I
Can't go to we go so easy. I don't like to go
Anyway, bars are expensive
They are yeah
Oh my god, I still haven't finished my heartlet maze the two are related to be tricky. I'm
Oh gosh
Five o'clock somewhere. Yeah, we didn't even know it. Okay. It's not you. Okay. Are you good?
Hello
Like he's purposely trying to get a rise out of me. You know that right? Just ignore
Almost falling down inside of your leg
I didn't see it Charlie. Did you show it? I don't think you showed it guys
Didn't you already see it? I didn't see it type of one in the chat if you saw his dick
If you want to see the psyche, you can just be backstage if you want.
Should we do it right now? You know to see my bath hall again. Do you want?
Yeah
And I'm just slowly drinking this whiskey, you know, yeah, that it's well, just drink just slam it down and go to bed
Just slam it down and get it over with I would do whatever you I'm yeah, we already know that because
You got the fake hair. You got the glasses. You got the kills. You got your shades drawn. Yeah
I don't know I'll have something here for you, baby
I have nothing for me. Well, Charlie said it was those ball they couldn't tell if they thought it or not
It looked like it could have done vagina
But hey, it's like it. Where is all I saw you off. You know good guys, you know, don't say I'm funny good guys
Who are the who are the good guys, what do you say? Would you say I say? Yeah, because like this
This grandmother is quite boring, you know, and we have something good actually here
Oh
I don't know what you look you have a question I say
Example it was just like an example because oh there's an example. Okay. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I don't know
He's a he's a driving around shirtless. I think it gives them back
Is a relative I don't know where he is. I use it. Yeah, sometimes people go
Maybe maybe I have some life
What do you think maybe he asked a lie or something? Yeah, yeah, maybe well, maybe he does maybe I don't he knows
Driving around with a body, you know European backpackers body there
Yeah, well it's going to you know
This thing happened
Did you catch that Christian?
Who will miss our European backpack or you know, that's what I'm getting lost
Yeah, just
I'm not going to live anywhere because I think Christie lives before me. Oh honey. I have all day
that
I have more than one phone so if I got
Phone calls or make phone calls. I can do it on my other phone
There's so many I have all day to bother you
your
Instead of all day
Like all day to irritate you all day
Mutta se oli todella hyvää ja hyvää asiaa, joissa ei nähnyt mitään järjestelmää täällä.
Mitä persoja olisit?
Mitä persoja?
Which person would I would I would mod Jamie's Cowboys probably
Jamie I hate Jamie's is I think yeah, yeah
Yeah
Yeah, what about the reality Nancy is a reality Nancy a good one
Yeah, yeah, I think I like reality Nancy. She's always been a good one. He's afraid you're gonna mod me
And I would play that I bought a Christian
Only Jamie should get the mod and she's very fair
But then you have to mod some party as well, you know, no it doesn't
Why does he
It's just that what happens is
Yes, that's a scholar too. Yeah, I know
We need to have like a two months feelings, you know, just
They are just oh, I don't like this today because I just have my periods
Or I might get a pass
You know you have to always stay hurry up and just slam it just take a big sweat swig out of it
There you go. Just just you don't need the glass. Don't dirty a glass
Let's take a shot but drink that baby down
Go ahead slam it let's see if you can slam it
Good job. Oh or not pour another
Money that's how it is down here all the time
What is that what is that thing it's over your over your crotch is that like a piece what is that what is that piece called?
Me what is it? What is that piece? No, what is that piece of fabric? Yeah, I
Flap yeah, what is that? What's that flap? Yeah, it's so when they walk it hits their penis, so it goes stays down
See how light it is outside psyche
Yeah, it's it's probably the same time it is here. That's what I was thinking
See how light it is outside
Yep
No, he's not over in Europe anyway or the job. What do you think this is from?
What is that is that a flashlight?
No, it's a what is that? What is that? I see a hole
What is that?
Which country this is from Europe? It's from Europe. What is that? Oh look how bright it is outside
We can see right through the the blind there you move the curtain over too far seal. Yeah
You could have made your bed this morning
You need you need darker shades if you want to keep that light out
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
It's like what are you doing psych?
What are you doing you tell me to come up and help me red scene and you turn up full screen
I'm like wait a minute
Oh, yeah
Are you slept last night? I know you weren't live at like midnight ish
Yeah, I said the I was asleep yesterday. So I was awake last night and then
I mean, I think I'm gonna go get a haircut today. Maybe and
Are you gonna shave all the way?
I'm pretty shaved still. I still I think I'm okay, so
Yeah, I'm uh, I'm lucky a little better. I bet my tears low low gray and
Oh
What do you have to say like wait, what do you why are you here?
Are you doing
Why do you keep lifting it why you keep lifting your skirt higher
Why do you do that
Yeah
You know we get to kick out of that he purposely does that just to irritate you my gosh
Well, I need to be tough to react to because that's people know what's not all but they were never they've already
Ignore him people to get it done and go away already
Yeah, no, okay, yeah, I'll be through it's here
You know
Road changer
Why are you eating that
That tastes pretty strong
No, thank you
Okay
Yeah, I'm gonna get a haircut
Uh, yeah, well, yeah, I'll go see him. I mean it's like I'm just trying to I don't know
I'd like to have things resolved. I'd like to have at least one answer right I give up
He's done. Thank you. I give anything. He's just like
What are you doing? Who are you? Are you here?
well
Oh
You don't have a sexy thigh, I just hate to break that news to you
Yes, you see a sexy thighs you said he does he does not oh he does not yeah
Hey, hey, I haven't like going you know before you put a kill time you go to a tanning salon and give me a little
Color on those on those pasty legs. I mean, I might have mine are bad, but I'm not I'm not gonna kill you know
Well, I did put on speedo, but
Give me like a give me like a one-minute morning before I'd say my son's motorcycle
Oh nice
Love it love the nice yellow color
Oh
Thank you Brian needs a new choir, so I wanted to get a new tire
Hi, it's pretty up today cloudy a little bit
upon
Beautiful day
That's kind of cloudy
Yeah, this guy is so blue. Yeah, it's blue behind the clouds
Pretty way out here
Yeah
Are you okay? Are you drunk?
Me? I'm not drunk.
Hey, Brian, Brian, did you wear underwear under your coat?
Christian, that looks like...
Bobby, go lay down.
Hi.
Yeah, drink it.
Okay, let's go. Okay, let's go.
Tristan, come on. You should say that.
What kind of grown-ass man sits up here just itching to expose himself?
Christine, you have nothing to offer here, just to bring that fucking nagging, so I'm just asking that, you know, it's not fair, you know, we are just having a good time, you know, just getting drunk wasted, you know, doing stupid stuff.
Okay, so you keep saying we, you keep saying we, I don't see Mr. Sight drinking, do you?
Mä oon aika yksinkertaisesti, mutta mä oon...
Se on hyvä. Hei, Psyki. Se on hyvä, että hän menee tämä...
Tämä ääni.
Olen välttämättä, mutta...
Täällä välttämättä on hyvä.
Täällä välttämättä.
Who I'm
But I'm on old man. I can do whatever you want and
I'm here for you
Am I older than you? I think I might be older than you. I'll be your old man. How old are you? I
Know what? Thank you. He's open. Yes. There was a six months
Sixties
Okay
Hey Doug, you're going to end up finding your way out of chat and it's going to be for more than a couple of minutes. Stop
That's why Doug does always comes in in that fake profile
Yeah, I wonder I wonder yeah, he also was trying to say that he was the Dougie T or the Dougie not no because Dougie Doug came in
Remember yeah, I remember it
But he said it wasn't but he said it wasn't yeah, yeah, but there's other one there's a couple of we know Dougie Doug
Yeah
My god
Look, okay, he's getting a little bit antsy. Look how high that's going up now. Oh
My god, oh
Yeah, purposely
Yeah
Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see
Are you supposed to wear a kills above your knees like that well he's supposed to wear it where you know
There's that little pin thing. He's unpinned his
The cream are those are cream drink
Okay, Doug one more
Soon you'll be weeding those people up those type of people up to
Right he's so full of shit
He's getting so drunk he can't even light it
I don't know what to do with the response.
Yeah, we're ready to go.
Hey, Harry, how are you?
Well, yeah.
The chat's just kind of weird.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff going on in it.
Slow.
People talking in itself.
I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I live, I
Okay, I took him off because he was playing like some some like sounds
And he was standing he was he's about to go up skirt. I know I know it's about you. So
Okay, I just smell it
Okay
What's he doing? How long?
Let's see back stage
Oh my god
Oh, no, his pants are still open.
Ah! Ah!
Okay.
Just leave him in the corner.
He's used...
Okay.
Oh!
You know if you turn your chat on and leave him over there, it'll cover more of it. You know that, right?
Now that why is the panel dead, uh, baby, is there seriously people here? It's not dead.
Now the panel is dead. Oh, why?
I'll say that because of course this old woman is always complaining that many people can't do
the sort of guy that you talk to. Let's chat, you know, rule this our shop, you have this, perhaps it's this.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Even if I could understand the words you're saying I don't understand what you mean. I mean, I can take out most of the words
But this doesn't make sense
What I'm saying you don't understand what I'm saying
Now say it again
I'm listening. Oh
Hello, I'm listening. Please tell me
I'm here
We know okay, I can never mind
I was just having a
You use OBS and you can just put
Okay
Yeah
It's gonna be different
different crowds coming different times, but
We never discovered here
So, are you talking to me?
Are you talking to me?
I'm sorry, that was the guy.
Um, there.
My gosh.
He said there.
Have there been cats you may have a chat I have a question for you. Yeah, now's your time to ask
I know yeah, I've been dying to ask questions ever everyone come on
on the panel you will put down
Pistilene or the last okay my god, and some of these questions are
How to make them?
Moves in the heat are up. I'm it will make it brighter. Okay. Yeah, I know
People should be streaming more sometimes. I'm the only one streaming
This is a hopper
This is how bad when people get from
her morning
She might still be right here and I saw I saw her alert coming from
You're trying to
Intercept what he was doing
He is he is totally out of decorum in a kilt that way. He would he's a Polly those that truly wear them
There is a proper decorum for them
That's going pretty fast. Doug, are you forgetting psych asked me to come up? He invited me. He didn't ask. He invited me to come up. You're welcome to come, Dougie, if you feel neglected.
Nobody's stopping you, sweetheart.
Everything is posted.
All is welcome.
Okay, proper kills. Our size will be still cover both legs, both thighs and creep down.
Even with one leg spread. Uh yeah, he's totally out of decorum for a kill. He he he's uh uh
Why is he?
Psych
Oh my goodness. You hit the wrong button.
Was that on accident or? Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's the right. You're the right
next to the solo layout and solo layout and group layout. So,
it's definitely, I don't want to see it. I didn't want to see what he moved. Oh, he moved.
I don't know. What's he doing backstage now? He's
I feel he's doing things. He's putting the balloons back up his pants.
It's too much
Where's your that's on your tooth. Oh, no, I said
Oh
You're off you got something on your teeth went down to the bottom now
Let's sit back up on this cigar. Sorry, thank you for the email everybody
Okay, so what's your okay, so you want it you don't plan
You don't want to do this trick
Yeah
Exactly, okay. Okay. Let's get back. Okay. What's wrong? I thought we're gonna go. No, you're being yourself to do
Thank you getting a
free show, yeah
You like to sell you thank you thank you buddy like to sell
Hope I'm doing okay. Yeah, but you're not you're not talking though. They say something. I
Am
She's not even talking now speaking what is wrong with you
Yeah, I'm just
Trying to say that why are you are trying to offend me? I'm not going to say
or show anything here.
I'm not gonna offend you.
I have nothing to show you.
I am trying to offend you.
To go so you will find some place else to hang.
I'm here to stay because I like the psyche.
I like all these people around here.
No, because you have no problem with risking his channel.
I have done nothing.
Not ready yet.
What is your problem? You are an old woman. Why you are on the internet? That's my problem.
Well, you're a pervert. But that's why you're on the internet, right?
I want your time here.
You're a pervert. That's why you're on the internet, right?
But you are here to argue with younger guys about...
Did you do... Maybe you need to...
Scroll back a bit because he asked me
I really don't care if you do or don't you don't affect my life
But christian I don't hate you but I don't but see you don't understand. I don't care if you do
I'm quite relaxed
I have to understand that, you know, in the internet we are doing our own business, you know, we are, we are crazy, you know.
You are not going to be in the internet. You have to understand.
My lady, everybody loves you, but don't, don't make everybody hate you, you know.
We are here to have a good time.
Mm-hmm.
We did good. We were just prepared.
Christine, you are not a bad person. Everybody knows that.
But you can control Internet.
Oh, shit. I'm thinking you are, though.
You can control Internet.
Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah, what are you doing?
Yeah
She'll pass
Samantha how are you?
That's Amanda
It's very good to thank you. It was glorious a patient
Tom Tom star all the people are a few performance for Tom the last time my friends like you know
He's like he went in the bathroom and the the Americans flag speeders on the floor. He's like, oh, yeah
I have and he said he has an American flag pattern thing
You're wearing a speedo. I didn't really tell him about my stream, but I
was like
So yeah, yeah, then I didn't tell me I didn't tell me to but
It's it's like a it's not a it's
He's got like a silk piece of cloth or something like a pillowcase over that chair that keeps sliding
Nobody puts on a national flag on them
Crown and Bernie nobody that's the least place
Nobody will never do that
if you burn America flag or
Albania flag is said nobody
Disrespectful see purposely got up to adjust his kill to show his thigh, you know
Yeah
Are you doing cover your thigh?
Not very pleasing to the eye
for males or females
I agree. There's nothing sexy about that thigh
Thigh, my thigh. Yeah, uh, Ilya? Ah
Cover yourself now. Okay. Do not try the thigh. Cover yourself.
Cover your foot. You're supposed to wear the quilt below the knees.
And it's supposed to be
Is it muscle or not you can hit me
It's not pleasing to the eye
It's like fat muscle skin and bone
It's pasty white
Yeah, it's whiter than I am
You're a pianist or a slave to the American people
Honey, if you think that's sexy, then um, we need to get you out of the house a little bit more sweetheart
Yeah, you know
It is a man. I know he looks like resuscitation Annie or was there a CPR in your something it's you know, it's this is
It's a white guy in that uh
That week that week
Okay, so Brian. Hey, Christina time
up, dude
Elias gives leg day. Oh, yeah, we're supposed to go to the gym today with that time. You can spend with us instead
Doug I'd be happy to leave panel. Is that what yeah, I should do since you want to control it and but you don't want to be up here
Just asking Doug
Tell me to leave the panel. Why don't you leave the chat?
Whoa
Don't be nasty to other people
How did he be a nasty to me?
It's good that nobody's around more you're demanding me to leave okay
Who says you need to leave?
There's a lot of places I can go and other things I can do.
Everybody, you just talk shit so much against me.
I am here to love you.
I'm here to love you, Grandmother.
I just love you so much.
But you talk all the shit from me.
I don't want to talk shit about you.
It is okay
Well, we invited the rest thing for the college
I'm sorry I said anything, but that's how it works.
Thank you
Thank you very much.